Given the astonishing potential of AI to transform our lives, we all need to take action to deal with our AI-powered future, and this is where AI by Design: A Plan for Living with Artificial Intelligence comes in.
鉴于人工智能具有改变我们生活的惊人潜力，我们都需要采取行动，应对由人工智能驱动的未来，而《人工智能设计：与人工智能共处的计划》一书恰好能在这方面派上用场。
This absorbing new book by Catriona Campbell is a practical roadmap addressing the challenges posed by the forthcoming AI revolution.
卡特里奥娜·坎贝尔的这本引人入胜的新书是一份实用的路线图，着眼于应对即将到来的人工智能变革所带来的种种挑战。
In the wrong hands, such a book could prove as complicated to process as the computer code that powers AI, but, thankfully, Campbell has more than two decades’ professional experience translating the heady into the understandable.
如果由不合适的人来写，这样一本书理解起来可能会和驱动人工智能的计算机代码一样复杂；不过，值得庆幸的是，坎贝尔拥有二十多年把高深内容转化为易懂文字的职业经验。
She writes from the practical angle of a business person rather than as an academic, making for a guide which is highly accessible and informative and which, by the close, will make you feel almost as smart as AI.
她不是以学者的身份，而是从商界人士的实用角度来写作，这使本书成为一本通俗易懂、信息丰富的指南，读到最后，你会觉得自己几乎和人工智能一样聪明。
As we soon come to learn from AI by Design, AI is already super-smart and will become more capable, moving from the current generation of “narrow-AI” to Artificial General Intelligence.
读了《人工智能设计》，我们很快就会了解到，人工智能已经超级聪明，而且还会变得更强大，从当前这一代“狭义人工智能”发展到通用人工智能。
From there, Campbell says, will come Artificial Dominant Intelligence.
坎贝尔说，再往后，就会出现主导型人工智能。
This is why Campbell has set out to raise awareness of AI and its future now — several decades before these developments are expected to take place.
正因如此，坎贝尔现在就着手提高人们对人工智能及其未来的认识，而这些发展预计要几十年后才会发生。
She says it is essential that we keep control of artificial intelligence, or risk being sidelined and perhaps even worse.
她说，至关重要的是，我们要保持对人工智能的控制，否则就有被边缘化的风险，甚至可能落得更糟的下场。
Campbell’s point is to wake up those responsible for AI — the technology companies and world leaders — so they are on the same page as all the experts currently developing it.
坎贝尔的用意是唤醒那些对人工智能负有责任的人——科技公司和世界各国领导人——让他们与目前所有正在开发人工智能的专家想法一致。
She explains we are at a “tipping point” in history and must act now to prevent an extinction-level event for humanity.
她解释说，我们正处在历史的“临界点”上，必须现在就行动，防止人类遭遇灭绝级别的事件。
We need to consider how we want our future with AI to pan out.
我们需要思考：我们希望与人工智能共处的未来如何发展。
Such structured thinking, followed by global regulation, will enable us to achieve greatness rather than bring about our downfall.
这样有条理的思考，再加上随后的全球监管，将使我们能够成就伟业，而不是自取灭亡。
AI will affect us all, and if you only read one book on the subject, this is it.
人工智能将影响我们每一个人；如果你只读一本关于这个话题的书，那就读这本吧。